슈퍼에 들려서 살게 있어
I'm just gonna run to the
store and get a few things.
이따 데리러 올게
I'll pick you up
when you're done.
Okay.
같이 있어주면 더 좋지만
허락하지 뭐
I like it a little better
when you stay, but all right.
쉘든 왔구나
Hey, Sheldon.
컷하러 왔는데
Hello. I'm here for my haircut
도노프리오 아저시 계세요?
with Mr. D'Onofrio.
미안한데 토니는
입원 중이라네
I'm sorry, Uncle Tony's
in the hospital.
상태가 좋지 않아
He's pretty sick.
도노프리오 아저씨가
병원에 있다니
Oh, dear, Mr. D'Onofrio's
in the hospital.
왜 나쁜 일은
나한테만 일어날까
Why do these things
always happen to me?
대신 해줄게
I can cut it for you.
도노프리오 아저씨가 아니잖아요
You're not Mr. D'Onofrio.
전 도노프리오
아저씨한테만 받아요
I get my hair cut
by Mr. D'Onofrio.
말도 안 되지?
You believe
this guy?
(murmurs)
잠시만요
Excuse us for a second.
쉘든, 괜찮을 거야
Sheldon, it's okay,
he can do it.
저 분도 이발사잖아
He's a barber.
이발사가 아니라
아저씨 조카야
He's not a barber,
he's the nephew.
뷰티산업에 확산되어 있는
친족 등용을 보여주고 있어
He's an example
of the kind
of nepotism that runs rampant
in the barbering industry.
디노프리오 아저씨는
내 스타일을 잘 알고 있어
Besides, Mr.
D'Onofrio knows
exactly how I like my
hair done because he has
텍사스에서 보낸 이발
내역을 갖고 계시니까
all my haircut records
from my barber in Texas.
무슨 소리야?
What are you talking about?
처음 이사왔을 때
When I first
moved here,
머리를 자르기 두려워서
I was nervous about
finding a new barber,
엄마가 이발 내역서를
이쪽으로 보내줬어
so my mother had all
my haircut records
sent here to
Mr. D'Onofrio.
이발 내역서는 존재하지 않아
There's no such thing
as haircut records.
있거든
Yes, there are.
본 적 있어?
Have you ever seen them?
엄마가 분명히 보냈다고 말했어
No, but my mother assured
me they were sent here,
내역서가 이분한테는
없다는 것에 1달러를 걸게
and I'll bet you
dollars to donuts
that this one
doesn't have them.
저기, 아저씨
Uh, excuse me.
제 이발 내역서를
갖고 계시나요?
Do you have access
to my haircut records?
뭐요?
Your what?
T.S. 엘리엇의 명언을
바꾸어 표현하면
To paraphrase T.S. Eliot,
이것이 세상이
끝나는 방식이다
this is the way
the world ends--
쾅 하는 포성이 아니라
조카와 같이 온다
not with a bang
but with a nephew.
쉘든, 넌 성인이야
저 분은 전문가이시고
Sheldon, you're a grown man,
he's a professional,
네가 원하는 컷은
1946년도 포스터에 있잖아
and your haircut is number three
on that poster from 1946.
우선 앉고
Just sit down
한번 믿어봐
and let him do it.
바보같이 잘라놓으면
네가 책임져
Fine, but if I come
out of this
looking like a dork,
it's on you.
(clears throat)
우리 애가 재밌는
얘기를 해줬는데
So my kid said
the funniest thing today.
이건 아니다
Nope.
나중에 이 얘기도
누군가에게 들려주겠죠?
When you tell this story later,
저희는 별나다는
표현을 자주 써요
the word we usually use is
"quirky."
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪
♪ Then nearly 14 billion years
ago expansion started... Wait! ♪
♪ The Earth began to cool ♪
♪ The autotrophs began to drool,
Neanderthals developed tools ♪
♪ We built the Wall ♪
♪ We built the pyramids ♪
♪ Math, Science, History,
unraveling the mystery ♪
♪ That all started
with a big bang ♪
♪ Bang! ♪
DC 기타 미국드라마 갤러리
The Big Bang Theory 5x18
The Werewolf Transformation
Original Air Date on February 23, 2012
자막 공대언니
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
파르메산 치즈 좀
Can you pass
the Parmesan cheese?
여기
Sure.
뭐하는 거야?
What are you doing?
머리카락이 눈을 가려서
I'm trying to get the hair
out of my eyes.
쉘든
LEONARD:
Sheldon,
하루 지연된 것 뿐이잖아
you are one day late
for your haircut.
내 악몽에 캡션을
달아줘서 고마워
Thank you for captioning
my nightmare.
출장 명령을 받았어
Lookie here,
I got my travel orders.
탑승 과학 기술자
하워드 왈로위츠에게
"Payload Specialist Howard
Wolowitz is requested
휴스턴 소재
NASA 존슨 우주 기지에서
"to report to the NASA
Johnson Space Center,
"Houston, Texas,
월요일 오전 8시부터
훈련이 예정되어 있습니다
for astronaut training
Monday 8:00 a.m."
NASA 안내문이니까
8시가 아니라 0800이야
Yeah, but it's from NASA,
so it's 0800.
오전 8시라고 되어 있어
But it says
"8:00 a.m""
0800라고 읽는 거야
You read it as "0800."
앞에 0이 적혀 있지 않아
It doesn't have an
"O" in front of it.
'오'가 있긴 있어
You know what does have
an "oh" in front of it?
오 마이 갓, 내가
우주 비행사라 질투하는구나
"Oh, my God, I'm an astronaut,
and you're dying of jealousy."
훈련에는 어떤...?
So, what kind of
things are they...?
그 짓 좀 그만할래?
Will you stop that?
어쩔 수 없어
10대 아이돌이 된 기분이야
I can't help it,
I feel like a teen heartthrob.
전에 동생 머리를
해준 적이 있는데
You know, Sheldon,
I used to cut my brother's hair.
내가 컷해줄까?
I could do it for you.
좋은 의도로
말한 건 알겠어
Penny, I know you mean well,
촌에서는 그렇게 했겠지
offering the skills
of the hill folk, but, um,
도시에서는
here in town,
버터를 직접 만들지 않고
we don't churn our own butter,
자루를 치마로 리폼하지 않아
we don't make dresses
out of gunny sacks,
역샘한 금발 여자한테
컷을 맡기는 건...
and, uh, we sure as shootin'
don't get our hair cut
by bottle-blonde...
쉘든, 못되게 굴지 마
Sheldon, be nice.
머리 때문에 나쁜
남자처럼 행동하게 되네
I'm sorry,
it's the bad boy attitude
that comes with this hair.
내가 가는 미용실은 어때
You could go to my guy.
베벌리힐스에
주안주안이라고 있어
He's at Juan-Juan
in Beverly Hills.
차도 마시고
두피 마사지도 받고
They bring you a cup of tea,
they'll massage your scalp.
200달러라서
좀 비싸긴 하지만
It's about $200, but sometimes
you look in the next chair
옆 자리에 토니 단자같은
연예인이 앉을 수도 있어
and you see a superstar
like Tony Danza.
뭐 좀 물어보자
WOLOWITZ:
Quick question here:
우주 비행사 훈련
소식을 방금 전했는데
Have we actually changed
the conversation
from "I'm going
to astronaut training"
헤어컷 얘기로
벌써 넘어갔어?
to "Sheldon can't
get a haircut"?
지금은 누가
질투를 하고 있지?
Now who's dying of jealousy?
오, 바로 너네
"Oh," it's you.
♪ I'm a cowboy ♪
♪ On a steel horse
I ride ♪
♪ I'm wanted ♪
♪ Wanted ♪
♪ Dead or alive. ♪
쉘든
Sheldon,
애인이랑 같이
노래 부르는 날이잖아
you're ruining girlfriend-
boyfriend sing-along night.
미안해
I'm sorry.
이발소를 찾고 있는데
시간이 부족해
I'm looking for a barber
and I'm running out of time.
머리가 1펨토초 당
4.6욕토미터나 자라고 있어
My hair is growing at the rate
of 4.6 yoctometers
per femtosecond.
조용히 하면 소리도 들려
I mean, if you're quiet,
you can hear it.
'슈퍼컷'은 어때?
What about Supercuts?
한번 간 적이 있는데
I tried once.
남녀를 같은
공간에서 다루더라
They do men's and women's hair
in the same room
at the same time.
헤어 무스를 추가한
소돔과 고모라야
It's like Sodom and Gomorrah
with mousse.
위기 상황은 아니네
Well, this isn't
a crisis.
머리는 좀 길어도 되잖아
Why don't you just let
your hair grow out a little?
머리는 좀 길어도 된다고?
Why don't I let
my hair grow out?
그럴 바엔 버켄스탁을 신고
Um, why don't I start
wearing Birkenstocks
남들한테 확인 받기 위해
and seeking validation
of my opinions by asking
Can you dig it이라고
물어보겠지
"Can you dig it?"
글쎄
Well, I don't know.
긴 머리를 하면
섹시해 보일 것 같아
I think you might look
sexy with long hair.
어깨 정도까지
내려오는 길이에
The kind that flows down
to your shoulders
말을 타면 바람에 휘날리고
and blows back
while riding on a horse.
맨몸과 넓은 가슴
Bareback and bare-chested.
양치 좀 하고 올게,
좀 걸릴 거야
I'm gonna go brush my teeth;
it might take a while.
안녕
Hi.
자기야
Hi, sweetie.
보고 싶어
I miss you.
나도
I miss you, too.
첫 날은 어땠어?
So tell me
all about your first day.
어디서부터 말하지
Oh, wow, where do I even start?
무중력 체험을 해봤어
I got to experience
zero gravity.
어떻게 하는건데?
Cool. How do they do that?
근사했어
It's pretty neat.
비행기를 타고
You get in this plane
20초 동안 올라가다가
that goes almost straight up
for, like, 20 seconds,
추락할 것처럼
다시 내려오는 거야
and then straight back down
like it's going to crash, and
그리고는 계속 반복하지
they do it
over and over again, you know,
토해도 멈추지 않아
no matter how many times
you throw up.
토했어?
You threw up?
재밌는 건 무중력 상태라
Yeah... and the craziest part
is, because there's no gravity,
분비물이 공중에 떠다녀
the throw-up kind of
floats there...
작은 덩어리로 뭉쳐서
in a little ball,
and
소리 지르느라
입을 벌리고 있잖아
if your mouth is open
because you're screaming...
가끔은 덩어리들이
다시 들어오지
...sometimes it just floats
right back in.
(laughing)
그럼 모두에게
비웃음을 당하지
Boy, does everyone laugh
at you when that happens.
못됐다
That sounds mean.
아냐
No.
나도 웃고 싶었는데
Yeah, I would have laughed, too,
덩어리가 다시
나올까봐 참았어
but I didn't want the vomit
to come back out.
(laughs)
Anyway...
부탁 좀 들어줄래?
Oh, could you do me a favor
속옷을 택배로 보내줘
and overnight me
some more underwear?
더 필요해?
Sure, why?
내일은 원심 분리기에
넣고 빙빙 돌릴건데
I got a look at the centrifuge
they're going to spin me
around in tomorrow,
너무 적게 챙긴 것 같아
and I have a hunch
I packed a little light.
(chuckles nervously)
도노프리오 아저씨?
Mr. D'Onofrio?
쉘든이에요
It's Sheldon.
기념품점에 이발사
관련 용품이 없더군요
They didn't have
anything barber-themed
in the gift shop,
so I got you this.
티셔츠에 문구 보이세요?
I don't know if you can read
his little T-shirt.
Get well bear-y soon
It says, um,
"Get well bear-y soon."
깨어있다면 아저씨도
재밌다고 생각했을 텐데
Trust me, if you were even
a little conscious right now,
you'd be laughing.
(laughs)
Anyway...
혼수 상태여도 주변을
인식할 수 있대요
There's new studies that show,
people in comas are aware
of everything going on
around them.
제 말이 들리면
With that in mind,
if you can hear me,
이쪽으로 다가오세요
move away from the light
가위질하는
소리를 향해서요
and toward the sound
of these scissors.
(door opens)
어떻게 도와 드릴까요?
Can I help you?
네
Yes.
가운 좀 빌릴 수 있나요?
Do you have something
I could use as a cape?
저런, 약을 안 먹고
Oh, dear,
did we spit out our pills,
9층에서 빠져나온
모양이구나?
slip out of the ninth floor,
and go on a little adventure?
아뇨
Oh, no,
컷하러 왔어요
no, I'm just here
to get my hair cut.
그렇군
I-I see.
잠시만 기달려라
J-Jus-Just wait here one moment.
경비 아저씨!
Security!
도망가야 해요
I got to run.
가위를 들고 있으니
뛰면 안되겠죠
But not with scissors--
that would be unsafe.
말을 여기로 옮기면
So, if I move
my horsey here...
내가 이긴거 아냐?
...isn't that checkmate
and I win?
Hmm.
이긴 거 맞아?
Well, is it
or isn't it?
여기서 잠시 쉬는 게
좋을 것 같아
You know, I think this is
a good stopping point.
네 첫 게임이고
Uh, it's your
first real game.
이 정도면 많이 배웠어
I threw a lot
of information at you.
Well, no,
왕이 갇혔잖아
I mean,
your king is trapped.
등대 때문에
이쪽으로도 못 오고
He can't go here
because of my lighthouse,
and...
뾰족한 모자 대문에
이쪽도 막혔어
he can't go here because
of my pointy-head guy.
아까 말했듯이
복잡한 게임이야
Like I said, complicated game.
내가 이겼어?
So did I win or not?
재미는 있었어?
Did you have fun?
재밌었다면
넌 승자야
Because if you had fun,
then you are, you are a winner.
체스는 재미로 하는 거니까
That's, that-that's
what chess is all about.
Hello.
- Hey.
- Oh, hey.
미안, 자리 옮길게
Sorry, Sheldon, I'll move.
Eh, why?
어느 자리에 앉던
무슨 상관이야
My spot, your spot--
what difference does it make?
방금 무슨 일이 일어났지?
Okay, what just happened?
몰라
I don't know.
네가 바비 피셔처럼
체스를 두고
Between you playing chess
like Bobby Fischer
쉘든이 아무 자리에나
앉으라고 하는걸 보니
and Sheldon being okay
with you in his spot,
누군가 과거로 돌아가
벌레를 밟아서
I'm guessing someone went
back in time, stepped on a bug,
미래를 바꿔 놓았나봐
and changed the course
of human events.
괜찮아?
Uh, sweetie,
are you all right?
아니
No, I'm not all right.
컷이 예정보다
6일 늦었는데
It's been six days since I
was supposed to get a haircut
아직 아무 일도 없었어
and nothing horrible
has happened.
이해가 안돼
Okay, I'm sorry,
I don't understand.
레너드, 설명 해줘
Leonard, explain it to her.
쟤는 미쳤어
Oh, uh, he's crazy.
지금까지 살면서
I have spent my whole life
세상의 질서 유지를 위해
trying to bring order
to the universe
모든 순간을 계획해왔어
by carefully planning
every moment of every day.
그런데 내 모든 노력이
But all my efforts--
저녁 메뉴, 잠옷
our dinner schedule,
my pajama rotation,
배변활동 스프레드시트
my bowel movement spreadsheet--
지금 생각하니
it's clear now,
모두 헛된 일이였어
I've been wasting my time.
저 역겨운 차트는 떼버리겠어
Good. I'm taking that
disgusting chart off the fridge.
You know, Sh-Sheldon,
가끔은 예측할 수
없는 것도 좋아
sometimes it's nice
not knowing what's coming.
나랑 레너드처럼
I mean, look at me and Leonard.
사귀다가 헤어졌다가
지금은 다시 만나잖아
We went out, we broke up,
now we're trying again.
앞으로의 일은 아무도 몰라
We don't know
what's gonna happen.
너네 사이는 뻔한걸
Oh, please, everyone knows
what's going to happen.
하지만 일리는 있어
But I see your point.
좋게 생각해
I think this could
be good for you.
변화를 줘도 괜찮잖아
Maybe it's time for you
to shake things up a bit.
그러네
You're right.
무질서를 받아들이겠어
I should embrace the chaos.
잘됐다
Great.
무엇부터 하려고?
What are you going
to do first?
글쎄
I don't know.
난 뭐든지 할 수 있어
I could do anything.
모든 계획은 무효야
All bets are off.
세상은 나의 것이다
The world is my oyster.
좋았어
I got it.
화요일 잠옷을 오늘 입겠어
I'm going to put
on my Tuesday pajamas tonight.
쉘든이 좀 걱정되네
I got to tell you,
I'm a little worried about him.
네 걱정부터 해
If I were you, I'd be
worried that a girl
체스를 처음 두는
여자한테 졌잖아
who's never played chess in
her life just kicked your ass.
Hi.
하위, 어떻게 된 거야?
Howie, what happened to you?
밤새 야생 서바이벌
훈련을 했어
We did overnight survival
training in the wilderness.
재밌었어
Big fun.
완전 재밌었지
Big, big fun.
좀 씻고 오려했는데
I was gonna freshen up for you
화장실 가는 길에
정신을 잃었어
but I blacked out a little
on the way to the bathroom.
서바이벌 훈련?
Survival training?
캠핑처럼?
Is that like camping?
Uh-huh.
먹을거리나 물은 없어
Except you don't
have food or water,
헤스 크레이머 캠프에서는
예배도 했었는데
and they don't have
a sunset Sabbath service
like they do
at Camp Hess-Kramer.
텐트에서 자?
Do you sleep in tents?
아니
No.
구멍 속에서 잤어
I slept in a hole
맨손으로 땅을 팠지
I dug in the ground
with my bare hands.
밤에 자던 도중에
And at some point
during the night,
아마딜로가 들어와서
an armadillo crawled in
날 안고 잤어
and spooned me.
불쌍해
Poor baby.
어쨌든 난 해냈어
But I did it.
살아남았어
I survived.
모래폭풍이 닥쳤을 때
죽을 것 같았지만
I wasn't sure I was going to
when the sandstorm hit.
터틀넥을 머리
위로 끌어올리고
I just pulled my turtleneck
up over my head
죽음을 기다렸어
and waited for death.
땀에 쩔은 보호막 속에
앉아 있으면서 깨달았어
But somehow as I sat there,
wrapped in a cocoon
of my own neck-sweat,
인간에게는 생존 본능이 있어
I found that primal part
of the human spirit
that just wants
to keep on living,
목숨은 무엇과도
바꿀 수 없어
no matter what the cost.
정말 용감하다
You're so brave.
자랑스러워
I'm proud of you.
나비도 먹었어
I ate a butterfly.
너무나도 작고...
It was so small and...
아름다웠는데
beautiful,
너무 배고팠어
but I was so hungry.
울어?
Are you crying?
아니, 그건 불가능해
No, I don't think it's possible.
탈수 상태거든
I'm severely dehydrated.
오줌이 치약 같아
My pee is like toothpaste.
하위, 힘들면 돌아와도 돼
Howie, if you're not able
to do this, come home.
널 다르게 생각하지 않을 거야
It won't change
how I feel about you.
고마워, 하지만
포기할 수 없어
Thanks, honey, but I can't quit.
우주 비행사가 될
기회를 차버리는 거잖아
If I do, I'll just be a guy
who had a chance to be an
astronaut and gave it up.
내가 도울 방법이 없을까?
Well, is there anything
I could do to help?
없어
No.
Wait.
속옷 좀 더 보내줘
Send more underwear.
(bongos playing in living room)
설마 쉘든이 봉고를
치는 건 아니겠지
Don't let this
be Sheldon playing bongos.
(bongos playing)
안녕, 레너드,
내 봉고 어때?
(rhythmically) Hello, Leonard,
do you like my bongos?
나한테 봉고가
있다는 건 몰랐지?
Bet you didn't know
that I had bongos.
쉘든, 새벽 3시야
Sheldon, it's 3:00 o'clock
in the morning.
새벽 3시는
3:00 in the morning
봉고에 딱이지
is a good time for bongos.
자고 있었어
I was sleeping.
내가 봉고를 치는 동안
레너드는 잔다
Leonard sleeps
while I play bongos.
잠이 와야지
No, he doesn't.
내가 봉고를 치는 동안
레너드는 못 잔다
Leonard no sleep
while I play bongos.
봉고 솔로
Bongo solo.
그만
Stop! Stop it!
Stop! Stop! Stop it!
대체 무슨 소리야?
- What the hell?!
- Oh, hi,
페니, 있잖아
Penny, guess what?
쉘든이 봉고를 구했어
Sheldon got bongos.
봉고는 갑자기 왜?
Why did you get bongos?
리처드 파인만도
봉고를 쳤잖아
Richard Feynman
played the bongos.
나도 해보고 싶었어
I thought I'd give that a try.
리처드 파인만은
유명한 물리학자였어
Richard Feynman
was a famous physicist.
레너드, 새벽 3시잖아
Oh, Leonard, it's 3:00 o'clock
in the morning.
파인만이 내 똥고에 사는
보라색 요정이라도 상관 안해
I don't care if Richard Feynman
was a purple leprechaun
who lived in my butt.
'was' 대신에 'were'를 써야지
Penny meant if he were
a purple leprechaun.
페니는 가정법 동사를
지키지 않았어
Penny forgot
to use the subjunctive.
쉘든, 이제 그만 자
Sheldon, go to bed.
내일 출근해야 되잖아
You have work in the morning.
아닐 수도 있지
Maybe, maybe not.
봉고 밴드를 만들고
월드 투어를 할 수 있잖아
Maybe tomorrow I start
a bongo band and tour the world.
잠깐
No, no, hang on,
uh, uh,
룸메이트 계약서
Roommate Agreement.
10시 이후에는
연주나 노래 금지
No hootenannies, sing-a-longs,
or barbershop quartets
after 10:00 p.m.
룸메이트 계약서?
Roommate Agreement?
장난해?
Are you kidding?
세상은 혼돈에 빠져있어
We are living in a world
of chaos.
룸메이트 계약서라니
Roommate Agreement.
어디 가?
Where are you going?
음악이 이끄는 곳으로
Wherever the music
takes me, kitten.
나는 봉고를 치며
I play bongos
계단을 내려간다
walking down the stairs.
(tumbling down stairs)
Oh! Oh!
계단을 내려갈 때는
봉고는 치지 말자
(playing bongos) Never play bongos
walking down the stairs.
(knocking)
서프라이즈
Surprise.
여긴 어쩐 일이야?
What are you doing here?
곁에 있어주려고
I'm here to help you
get through this.
널 돌봐줄 사람이 필요해
You can't do it on your own,
you need someone
to take care of you.
사랑해
Oh, I love you so much.
Oh, I love you.
하워드,
목욕 물이 다 식잖아
MRS. WOLOWITZ: Howard,
your bath is getting cold!
걱정 마,
엄마가 잠들면
Don't worry, once
she falls asleep,
아마딜로처럼 안아줄게
I'll spoon you
like an armadillo.
새벽에 봉고를
치면서 찾아왔어
He showed up in the middle
of the night with his bongos.
음악으로 유혹하는
줄 알고 좋아했어
I foolishly thought it was some
sort of musical booty call.
저런
Poor guy.
정말 피곤하겠다
He must have been exhausted.
레너드가 봉고를 치고
쉘든은 잠을 잔다
Sheldon like to sleep
while Leonard play the bongo!
그럴 필요는 없었잖아
That was kind of uncalled for.
아니, 그래야 했어
No, it was called for.
무슨 일이야?
What's going on?
쉘든
All right, Sheldon,
이런 미친 짓은
그만 하자
this craziness
has gone on long enough.
머리는 내가 잘라줄게
Please come home
so I can cut your hair.
페니, 넌 자격증이 없잖아
Penny, you're not trained.
You're not licensed.
내 이발 내역을
본 적도 없고
Most importantly, you don't have
access to my haircut records.
내 말 좀 들어봐
All right, honey, look,
우리는 오래 동안
친하게 지냈지?
we've known each other
for a long time now, right?
디즈니랜드에 데려갔고
I've taken you to Disneyland,
널 괴롭히는 애도 혼내주고
I kicked a bully
in the nuts for you,
너가 아플 때면
'소프트 키티'도 불러주고
I sing you "Soft Kitty"
when you're sick,
한번은 내 알몸도 봤잖아
you've even saw me naked once.
뭐라고?
I'm sorry,
what?
설명하자면 길어
It was a long story.
쉘든, 난 자신 있어
Anyway, Sheldon, I promise
I know what I'm doing.
허락해줘
Please let me cut your hair.
에이미, 어떻게 생각해?
Amy, what do you think?
이 여자라면 내 몸에
자라는 털을 다 맡길래
There's not a hair on my body
I wouldn't let this woman trim.
그래, 가자
Fine, let's go.
소파에 재워줘서 고마워
Thank you for letting me
sleep on your couch.
침대에서 자면 어떠냐고
권유하는 건 이제 지쳤어
There's only so many times
a woman can say,
"How about the bed?"
쉘든이 뭘 봤다는 거야?
What's this
about Sheldon seeing you naked?
진정해, 엉덩이랑 가슴만 봤어
Oh, relax. It was just
her bottom and her breasts.
거의 다 됐어
Almost done.
머리를 다 자르고 나면
At the end of the haircut,
도노프리오 아저씨는
야한 농담을 해줬어
Mr. D'Onofrio
would tell me a dirty joke.
난 그런 농담 몰라
Sorry, I don't know
any dirty jokes.
됐어, 어차피
이해한 적 없어
That's okay,
I never understood them anyway.
어때?
Okay, what do you think?
Hm, well,
약간 할리우드 스타일이지만
it's a little Hollywood.
나한테는 어울리네
But I think
I can pull it off.
잘했어
Well done, Penny.
내가 뭐랬어
Ha, told you.
이제 정리만 하면 끝나
Okay, I'm just gonna clean up
your neck a little
and then you are good to go.
Fun time.
(giggles)
미안, 간지러움을
타는 편이라
Sorry, sometimes the clippers
tickle me.
Okay.
(laughs)
이제 됐다
Okay, yep, we're all done now.
It's just... it's good.
그건 이리 줘
Let me just take that
away from you.
고마워
- Okay.
- Thank you very much.
You are welcome.
(door closes)
이사 가야겠다
Yeah, I'm gonna have to move.
공대언니 블로그
http://tbbt.tistory.com
== sync, corrected by elderman ==